http://www.hammacher.com/editorial/ccpa-privacy-notification-california/?promo=editorial#personalInformationSalesOOR

New Arrivals
Infants & Toddlers (0-3)
Kids (4-7)
Tweens & Teens (8+)
New Arrivals
Infants & Toddlers (0-3)
Kids (4-7)
Tweens & Teens (8+)
Join Email List
This Privacy Notice for California Residents supplements the information contained in our Privacy Policy and applies solely to all visitors, users, and others who reside in the State of California ("consumers" or "you"). We adopt this notice to comply with the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (CCPA) and any terms defined in the CCPA have the same meaning when used in this Notice.
Disclosures of Personal Information for a Business Purpose
In the preceding twelve (12) months, we have disclosed the following categories of personal information for a business purpose:
Identifiers.
California Customer Records personal information categories.
Commercial information.
Internet or other similar network activity.
Geolocation data.
Inferences drawn from other personal information.
Additionally, we disclose personal information for a business purpose to the following categories of third parties:
Service providers
Print Marketing Catalogue mailers
Email Service Promotion Providers
Delivery Carriers / Drop Shippers
Mail Planning Agency
List Brokers
List Managers
List Co-ops
On-Line Marketers
Fraud Risk Processors
From time to time we may share our postal mailing list with selected providers of goods and services that may be of interest to you. The following category of third parties apply:
List Managers
Use of Personal Information
We may use, sell, or disclose the personal information we collect for one or more of the following purposes:
To fulfill or meet the reason you provided the information. For example, if you share your name and contact information to ask a question about our products or services, we will use that personal information to respond to your inquiry. If you provide your personal information to purchase a product or service, we will use that information to process your payment and facilitate delivery. We may also save your information to facilitate new product orders, provide warranty services or process returns.
To provide, support, personalize, and develop our Website, products, and services.
To create, maintain, customize, and secure your account with us.
To process your requests, purchases, transactions, and payments and prevent transactional fraud.
To provide you with support and to respond to your inquiries, including to investigate and address your concerns and monitor and improve our responses.
To personalize your Website experience and to deliver content and product and service offerings relevant to your interests, including targeted offers and ads through our Website, third-party sites, and via email or text message (with your consent where required by law).
To help maintain the safety, security, and integrity of our Website, products and services, databases and other technology assets, and business.
For testing, research, analysis, and product development, including to develop and improve our Website, products, and services.
To respond to law enforcement requests and as required by applicable law, court order, or governmental regulations.
As described to you when collecting your personal information or as otherwise set forth in the CCPA.
We collect information that identifies, relates to, describes, references, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer, household, or device ("personal information").
Personal information does not include:
Publicly available information from government records.
Deidentified or aggregated consumer information.
[Information excluded from the CCPA's scope, like:
health or medical information covered by the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996 (HIPAA) and the California Confidentiality of Medical Information Act (CMIA) or clinical trial data;
personal information covered by certain sector-specific privacy laws, including the Fair Credit Reporting Act (FCRA), the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) or California Financial Information Privacy Act (FIPA), and the Driver's Privacy Protection Act of 1994.]
In particular, [our Website has/we have] collected the following categories of personal information from its consumers within the last twelve (12) months:
Category
What we collect
A. Identifiers.
A real name, alias (if provided), postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address or account name.
B. Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e)).
A name, address or telephone number. Some personal information included in this category may overlap with other categories.
D. Commercial information.
Products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies.
F. Internet or other similar network activity.
Browsing history, search history, information on a consumer's interaction with a website, application, or advertisement.
K. Inferences drawn from other personal information.
Profile reflecting a person's preferences.
Your Rights and Choices
The CCPA provides California residents with specific rights regarding their personal information. This section describes your CCPA rights and explains how to exercise those rights.
Access to Specific Information and Data Portability Rights
You have the right to request that we disclose certain information to you about our collection and use of your personal information over the past 12 months. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request (see Exercising Access, Data Portability, and Deletion Rights), we will disclose to you via hardcopy:
The categories of personal information we collected about you.
The categories of sources for the personal information we collected about you.
Our business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling that personal information.
The categories of third parties with whom we share that personal information.
The specific pieces of personal information we collected about you.
If we sold or disclosed your personal information for a business purpose, two separate lists disclosing: sales, identifying the personal information categories that each category of recipient purchased; and disclosures for a business purpose, identifying the personal information categories that each category of recipient obtained.
Deletion Request Rights
You have the right to request that we delete any of your personal information that we collected from you and retained, subject to certain exceptions. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request (see Exercising Access, Data Portability, and Deletion Rights), we will delete (and direct our service providers to delete) your personal information from our records, unless an exception applies.
We may deny your deletion request if retaining the information is necessary for us or our service provider(s) to:
1. Complete the transaction for which we collected the personal information, provide a good or service that you requested, take actions reasonably anticipated within the context of our ongoing business relationship with you, fulfill the terms of our Lifetime Guarantee or product recall conducted in accordance with federal law, or otherwise perform our contract with you
2. Detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, or prosecute those responsible for such activities.
3. Debug products to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.
4. Exercise free speech, ensure the right of another consumer to exercise their free speech rights, or exercise another right provided for by law.
5. Comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act (Cal. Penal Code § 1546 et. seq.).
6. Engage in public or peer-reviewed scientific, historical, or statistical research in the public interest that adheres to all other applicable ethics and privacy laws, when the information's deletion may likely render impossible or seriously impair the research's achievement, if you previously provided informed consent.
7. Enable solely internal uses that are reasonably aligned with consumer expectations based on your relationship with us.
8. Comply with a legal obligation.
9. Make other internal and lawful uses of that information that are compatible with the context in which you provided it.
Exercising Access, Data Portability, and Deletion Rights
To exercise the access, data portability, and deletion rights described above, contact us by:
Emailing us at CustomerPrivacy@hammacher.com
Calling us Toll-Free at 1-800-543-3717 or
Send your request to Customer Privacy, 9180 Le Saint Drive; Fairfield, Ohio 45014-5475
Please include your full name, street address, phone and e-mail address with your request.
We will then send you a Verifiable Request Form and instructions for making your request.
Only you, or someone legally authorized to act on your behalf, may make a verifiable consumer request related to your personal information. Making a verifiable consumer request does not require you to create an account with us.
You may also make a verifiable consumer request on behalf of your minor child. To designate an authorized agent, you must provide a Power of Attorney or a guardianship document for a minor child with your Verifiable Request Form.
You may only make a verifiable consumer request for access or data portability twice within a 12-month period. The Verifiable Request form and associated documentation must:
Provide sufficient information that allows us to reasonably verify you are the person about whom we collected personal information or an authorized representative, which may include a completed Verifiable Request Form and Proof of address such as a current utility bill.
We cannot respond to your request or provide you with personal information if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the personal information relates to you.
We will only use personal information provided in the Verifiable Request Form and associated documentation to verify the requestor's identity or authority to make the request.
For instructions on exercising sale opt-out rights, see Personal Information Sales Opt-Out Rights.
Response Timing and Format
We endeavor to respond to a verified consumer request within forty-five (45) days of its receipt. If we require more time (up to 90 days), we will inform you of the reason and extension period in writing.
If you have an account with us, we will deliver our written response to the address on that account. If you do not have an account with us, we will deliver our written response by mail to the address you provide on the Verifiable Request Form.
Any disclosures we provide will only cover the 12-month period preceding the verifiable consumer request's receipt. The response we provide will also explain the reasons we cannot comply with a request, if applicable. For data portability requests, we will provide you with a hardcopy of the data we have collected.
We do not charge a fee to process or respond to your verifiable consumer request unless it is excessive, repetitive, or manifestly unfounded. If we determine that the request warrants a fee, we will tell you why we made that decision and provide you with a cost estimate before completing your request.
Personal Information Sales Opt-Out Rights
If you are 16 years of age or older, you have the right to direct us to not sell your personal information at any time (the "right to opt-out"). We do not sell the personal information of consumers we actually know are less than 16 years of age.
To exercise the right to opt-out, you (or your authorized representative) may submit a request to us by:
Emailing us at CustomerPrivacy@hammacher.com
Calling us Toll-Free at 1-800-543-3717 or
Send your request to Customer Privacy, 9180 Le Saint Drive; Fairfield, Ohio 45014-5475
Please include your full name, street address, phone and e-mail address with your request.
Non-Discrimination
We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your CCPA rights. Unless permitted by the CCPA, we will not:
Deny you goods or services.
Charge you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through granting discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties.
Provide you a different level or quality of goods or services.
Suggest that you may receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or
quality of goods or services.
Please visit this privacy page often as our policies change from time to time.
Last updated on 2/24/2020
AMERICA'S LONGEST RUNNING CATALOG
Our Rather Famous Lifetime Guarantee
The products we offer are as unique as our name and our merchandise is backed by our Lifetime Guarantee of Satisfaction.
The independent Hammacher Schlemmer Institute was created in 1983 to rigorously research, test and rate products to make the Best products available to our customers.
Employee Owned
As an employee owned company, our customers are served by those with a vested interest in ensuring complete customer satisfaction.
Be the first to know about our unique new products
Email Address
Join
You are now subscribed to Hammacher emails -- Thank You!
Copyright 2020 Hammacher Schlemmer & Company, Inc.
All Rights Reserved · W108RP
Thank you for subscribing to Hammacher Schlemmer email/catalog.
You can expect to hear from us periodically about:
